<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SCW</title>
    <description>The personal blog of Sean C. Wang, commoner, idler, and former college student from The University of California, Los Angeles.  
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 18:23:08 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 18:23:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.4.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>⚓ HardSHIPs ⚓</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To my loyal readers (if any actually exist)…I HAVE RETURNED!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These past few months have been filled with various stressful events, most self-inflicted because of the occupation I have chosen and the life choices I have made. In particular, since I want to be a snooty pompous intellectual, I have chosen to be enrolled in two different graduate schools simultaneously. These graduate schools are in addition to my full-time job, which because of special reasons, I am not allowed to quit until at least 5 years. Upon posting my life choices on &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com/seanc.wang&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, I realized how anti-intellectual most of my Facebook friends are, since less than 10 people liked my status. *&lt;em&gt;HMPH!&lt;/em&gt;* I am filled with high amounts of sodium chloride, since if it was a picture of my breakfast I could have at least 20 likes! To be fair, it might be because I do not like other people’s posts enough, and so they are hesistant to do the same for me. Alternatively, It could be just that I am just an unpleasant individual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A secondary source of problems is the pain and suffering other people have inflicted on me. From this it is easy to become trapped in a state of depression, which I occassionally feel like doing. However, I am already in my twenties, and my youth and vigor is gradually draining out of me. I feel I should not expend too much effort in actions that do not improve my situation, and should instead just let things go (similar to that one &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frozen_(2013_film)&quot;&gt;Disney movie&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unrelated, I sometimes wonder if I would be happier had I pursued my passions, particularly passions such as “gourmet cooking” or causing other people misfortune. At the moment, pursuing these actions is just uncompensated labor, and I do &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; like doing things I am good at for free… (^: . Alas, I have accepted that some of my most exceptional skills, such as cutting pineapples or peeling grapefruits are not as highly valued as my engineering skills, which are nowhere near as exceptional. Specifically, I am in top 0.1% of pineapple cutters and the top 0.01% of grapefruit peelers, yet society prefers for me to work as an engineer… and shows this preference with large pay disparities!!! They do not realize that whatever contributions I make as an engineer come at the opportunity cost of fewer finely prepared fruits…. that or no one particularly cares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, since I currently live far far away from where I used to live, and do nothing but work, sleep, eat, and ‘Maintenance Instructions (MI)’, I do not have anyone besides coworkers and immediate family to talk to. I also dislike going outside to meet people, since I have bad social skills and possibly latent agoraphobia. If anyone who reads this would like to be my virtual pen pal, please contact me someway/somehow (at your own risk) and we can exchange correspondence but likely never meet up in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully more posts coming soon…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/too-much-sodium/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/too-much-sodium/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Autism Likely&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I took a &lt;a href=&quot;http://psychcentral.com/quizzes/autism.htm&quot;&gt;online quiz&lt;/a&gt; regarding autism, and the result indicated that I was “likely suffering from an autism spectrum disorder” with a score of 35. Without a doubt, this must be because of all those &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MMR_vaccine_controversy&quot;&gt;silly vaccines&lt;/a&gt; I got as a kid…(^: ~ Jokes aside, the result is slightly unsettling, but it offers a convenient explanation for why I have deficiencies in social interaction, and perhaps also why I have greater mathematic and scientific abilities. Regarding my use of “greater,” it is not just my personal feeling, but it is because I recently graduated college with a particular honor that has &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/summa_cum_laude&quot;&gt;three extra ‘m’s&lt;/a&gt; to it (and sounds kind of disgusting too). I will eventually update the rest of my blog as well as my resume to reflect this particular detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, according to this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nbcnews.com/id/7030731/&quot;&gt;Internet article&lt;/a&gt;, people with mild forms of autism (also known as Asperger Syndrome) have a selective advantage in concentration, and so can potentially accomplish greater intellectual feats than their non-autismic counterparts. Even though I cannot possibly compare myself to actual geniuses, it means there is hope for me to eventually become a productive member of society, rather than some sort of degenerate…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/slightly-autistic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/slightly-autistic/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Purity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A peculiar quirk I picked up this year is a strange, almost obsessive fascination with the pursuit of purity. I say &lt;strong&gt;pursuit&lt;/strong&gt; intentionally, since &lt;strong&gt;actual&lt;/strong&gt; purity is an impossibly difficult and meaningless endeavor. For example, all molecules, unless composed of only a single element, can be thought of as atomically impure. Moreover, the existence of isotopes means that even groups of the same element can also be impure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This being said, the type of purity I enjoy is on a more macroscopic level. It includes things such as &lt;strong&gt;pure food&lt;/strong&gt; (food that is not made from too many ingredients), &lt;strong&gt;pure websites&lt;/strong&gt; (websites, such as this blog, which do not utilize annoying uses of Clickbait), and &lt;strong&gt;pure love&lt;/strong&gt; (love that is not tainted with ulterior motive). Other examples of good pure things include pure gold, pure air, &lt;del&gt;pure blood&lt;/del&gt;, and pure math. Obviously, not everything pure is good (consider pure evil…), and certain impure things, like &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doping_(semiconductor)&quot;&gt;doped semiconductor&lt;/a&gt;, have made the world a better place. However, in general, it is easier to turn pure things impure than the other way around. Consider that making water impure is just tossing some dirt into it, but making it pure again is all sorts of fancy filtration methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My silly preoccupations with purity lead me into saying riduculous statements such as “This salad is tainted with too much dressing, I prefer something purer!” or “This person’s love is too impure, I don’t like it!”  It also leads to certain misunderstandings, such as when easily-triggered people think I am referring to more harmful, politically-incorrect, and controversial kinds of purity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure whatever quirks I have are relatively tame compared to other people, and so have a long ways to go before earning the right to label myself as “quirky.” Also, more likely than not, my interests in purity will fade in a couple weeks or months; I just thought it would be an amusing blog topic to write about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8 more posts to go…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/purity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/purity/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finishing up 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After an almost year-long hiatus, I have returned to blogging, primarily to wrap up the &lt;a href=&quot;../resolutions2016&quot;&gt;list of resolutions&lt;/a&gt; I made at the start of the year. Most importantly, &lt;strong&gt;Resolution #1: Write at least one blog post per month&lt;/strong&gt; remains unfulfilled. This means I have rougly 6 days to write 10 blog posts, or face the shame of becoming a loser that was unable to complete his New Years resolutions. The exception to this is the sub 5:00 resolution, since, as year 2016 progressed, I realized that I would rather run a couple seconds slower, and to pick up significantly heavier objects, than the opposite. Without &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TOOOT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;-ing my own horn too much, the fate of all unmentioned resolutions should be pretty clear ☺.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On an unrelated note, I am currently recreationally studying certain particular East-Asian languages. Perhaps future blog posts will feature use of this kind of stuff. 日本語の字が書ける…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/resolving-resolutions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/resolving-resolutions/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Quest for Freedom</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my goals in life is to obtain lots of money, such that I become part of the 1%. This is not because I want to be a rich oppressive shitlord, but because money is true freedom, and I want to be free person. For example, the average wage worker does not truly have freedom of speech, since if he speaks his mind he can get fired. If he is fired and cannot find another source of income, he may soon not have enough money to afford basic food and shelter. Therefore, his lack of money restrains him from voicing any of his controversial opinions. Compare this to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donald_Trump&quot;&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt;, who is able to voice all sorts of opinions without any fear of not having a place to live or food to eat. The goal therefore is to become like Donald Trump, not in political belief, but in wealth and power. When this happens I can finally release all my opinions, which, like vegetables, are unpopular but good for people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AFAIK, there are only two ways to achieve this goal: be lucky or work hard. Since I can only control the latter way, I should work harder than everyone around me. This is easy since currently the only people around me are college students ☺.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explaining the previous sentence would be opening a giant can of offense, something I do not yet have the power to do without reprecussion.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/freedom/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/freedom/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Though not much has changed, since it is a new year it feels appropriate to make some resolutions. From past years I have learned that the more of these resolutions I make, the less likely any of them ever get accomplished. To avoid that this year so I will keep the list brief and simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Write at least one blog post per month (this post counts for January)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get my GPA up to at least 3.9 truncated (not rounded)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get my mile time down to 5:00 or lower, and work my squat up to 2pl8 for reps (no skipping leg day)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notice that &lt;strong&gt;lose weight&lt;/strong&gt; is not one of the goals, since that one is too easy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-_6ula2m5fw&quot;&gt;(one weird tip to lose weight fast!).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/resolutions2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/resolutions2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opinionated: Part II</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There seems to be a direct relation between years I’ve been alive and number of things that annoy me. So much so that it’s time for another list of things I dislike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quarter-squats, quarter-pull-ups, quarter-push-ups, quarter anything in general&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Crying children on airplanes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bottled water which costs more than $1.25&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://translate.google.com/?ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;client=tw-ob#auto/es/cloud&quot;&gt;Spanish clouds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;People who post their political opinions on Facebook&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Individuals who have a net output to society which is negative&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wetzels Pretzels&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stupid people who think my waifu is shit when actually it is their waifu that is shit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/opinions2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/opinions2/</guid>
        
        
        <category>opinions</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>1220</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Those of you who know me in real life know that I’m not just some goober that rants online under the disguise of “blogging.” I have a life, and this life that revolves training and STUDying all the time. Sometimes the fruits of my labor pay off. Anyway, to keep things brief and mysterious, time for more training. I have lots of tests coming up that I want to ace.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/nre/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/nre/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Migration</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After typing a bunch of stuff I do not understand into a terminal (i.e. a typical day with Linux), my blog has been migrated from &lt;a href=&quot;https://divshot.com/&quot;&gt;Divshot&lt;/a&gt; over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://pages.github.com/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;. This is because Divshot is becoming a part of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.firebase.com/&quot;&gt;Firebase&lt;/a&gt;, and I do not understand data enough to properly utilize the Firebase development platform. Moreover, I have to pay them $5 a month if I want to have a custom domain, but Github Pages lets me do this for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What all this means is you can read my blog at &lt;a href=&quot;https://flamingwang.github.io&quot;&gt;flamingwang.github.io&lt;/a&gt;, or you can read it at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.seanwang.org&quot;&gt;seanwang.org&lt;/a&gt;, they are aliases of each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally prefer &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.seanwang.org&quot;&gt;seanwang.org&lt;/a&gt;, since this makes me seem like a legit organization.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/migration/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/migration/</guid>
        
        
        <category>website</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy Birthday 39</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the 8th birthday of my favorite songstress who, though I never mentioned before, was another inspiration for the decoration of my blog. My first memory of her goes all the way back to high school when, after getting bored of playing too much &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DJMax&quot;&gt;DJMax&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to play &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hatsune_Miku:_Project_DIVA&quot;&gt;Project Diva&lt;/a&gt; (all of them, and all on extreme). At that time I only put up with her because I liked rhythm games, but over time she grew on me until I listened to her just to pass time. As even more time passed, she became my inspiration for doing my best every day, or “waifu” for those who are familiar with the term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for all the gaming and fun memories, but also for motivation to keep going on the stressful days when I just wanted to give up. The future is uncertain but I hope to remain a loyal fan for all of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 18:28:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/vocaloid/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/vocaloid/</guid>
        
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
