<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SCW</title>
    <description>The personal blog of Sean C. Wang, commoner, idler, and former MSOL college student from The University of California, Los Angeles.  
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:50:30 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:50:30 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recovery</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Note: Upon drafting this I realized how much I sound like an emo teenager.  I decided to post it anyway incase someone finds it relatable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I have started to wonder criteria should be used to measure my recovery from traumatic heartbreak.  The ideas that come into mind are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gradually Subsiding Self-loathing:&lt;/strong&gt;  Though a baseline amount of self-loathing has existed since the beginning of time, I sincerely hope that most of my current self-loathing will eventually dissipate.  Either that or the higher amount is the now new normal and I will just have to deal with it.  The self-loathing makes me become more forgiving of flaws in others, because I know firsthand the depths of depravity that can be induced by severe sadness.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Re-emergence Hope in the Future:&lt;/strong&gt;  I optimistically tell myself tomorrow, if I can survive until then, will lead to less pain.  Although I already feel &lt;em&gt;OLD&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;FILLED&lt;/em&gt; with &lt;em&gt;MOLD&lt;/em&gt;, a friend of mine recently told me that &quot;black don’t crack, and asian don’t raisin&quot;.  This feels slightly fetishistic but I might as well use it to my advantage if life is forcing my hand.  I start to empathize more with glucose companions, as a fraction of them may just be formerly kind souls, tormented and corrupted by into robbing cradles by the suffering they faced during their younger years.  All this said there is also something to be said about keeping death in sight to be more mindful of life.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unclouded Evaluations of Others:&lt;/strong&gt;  I am the type of person that is only capable of serial dating, which means I leave all my eggs in one basket and cry about it when it doesn't work out.   A more multi-dating approach is too mentally exhausting, and is not necessarily more efficient because multi-dating is technically (or one would hope is) &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Round-robin_scheduling&quot;&gt;round-robin&lt;/a&gt; rather than true parallel.  I am currently working towards trying to evaluate new people based on their own personal set of attractive qualities, instead of purely measuring &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hamming_distance&quot;&gt;code distance&lt;/a&gt; to the previous.  I suppose full recovery is when the former starts to occur naturally, and without significant mental energy expended.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blog Post Frequency:&lt;/strong&gt;  I have unfortunately discovered the secret ingredient to prolific blog writing is profound sadness.  So much so that that if I stop posting it means  it either means lost the will to live or no longer possess the critical mass of sadness needed to write quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/more-writing-sadness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/more-writing-sadness/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dating</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Master of Romance: Part II</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As promised, below is my post about dating apps.  I usually never write this quickly but turns out writing is a good way to mitigate crippling sadness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tinder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I readily admit I do not get a lot of matches here.  However, I suspect matches follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boltzmann_distribution&quot;&gt;thermodynamic distributions&lt;/a&gt;, meaning one gets exponentially fewer matches simply by raising their standards.  The reverse is probably also true.  Sadly my experiences have given me Tinder PTSD so I will likely never return (or at least not until forced to do so by thirst).  Special shout-outs to Anna Pond-Lumber, who was the only person I met on the app that I thought was genuinely interesting, non-laborious to talk to, and most importantly kind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coffee Meets Bagel (CMB)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar to Tinder, I rarely get any matches, but this is probably because I am afforded enough profile space to traumatize potential suitors.  Moreover, I am convinced anyone who doesn’t like vocaloid music swiping on my profile is equivalent to those wanting hookups swiping on &quot;no hookups&quot; bios ..&lt;em&gt;cough cough cough&lt;/em&gt;..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CMB was the first app I used and so naturally the first time I got ghosted, where I met my ex-gf, and where to my chagrin I realized unclothed profile photos unanimously recieved a more favorable reception compared to clothed ones.  One thing that bothers me is the app’s strange bean currency, which allows users to buy matches or to increase the advertising of their profile.  The transactional nature of this bean economy and the fact that there are no other uses for beans has never sat well with me.  Also unique to this app is a rather high amount of low effort profiles.  I suspect the low effort profiles are a form of shielding ones pride, since rejection hurts a lot less if you were sandbagging compared to if you were putting forward your best efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tantan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No idea why (just kidding I know why) but I seem to get an abnormally high amount of matches using this app.  This leaves me overwhelmed and gives me too much anxiety to ever risk swiping right.  Also, no idea what happened to one of my only matches, but I heard she got knocked up and is now living somewhere with her cute babies.  All this said Tantan is the only app that lets me feel like I am a normal person, which is refreshing because being &quot;exotic&quot; is occasionally exhausting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bumble&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember trying this app once… only to get banned within minutes for shirtless mirror selfies.  Otherwise, my good friend &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/kathleen.jpeg&quot;&gt;Kathleen Fisher&lt;/a&gt; tells me it’s alright.  She’s rather popular and is quite annoyed the app is so pushy in forcing her to verify herself, suggesting it’s impossible for such beauty to be real.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/writing-sadness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/writing-sadness/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dating</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Uncluttered Chest</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Though I told my readers to expect another post on dating apps, I am a flawed human being who spent the entire interim in a love-induced haze and am only right now recovering.  I am compelled to write this blog post to get closure, and will return to regular scheduled programming at a later date.   If this bothers you just realize no one is forcing you to read my blog but yet you are here anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, I met a girl on Tinder, fell embarrassingly in love with her, then got dumped and so cried for the first time in over a decade.  However tempting it is to resent the other party, and even perhaps to become emotionally-walled and consider manipulating later partners, I try my best to try to salvage kind and &lt;a href=&quot;../dating-advice/&quot;&gt;conscience-preserving&lt;/a&gt; lessons learned.  Admittedly, I am also acutely aware that I delude myself into thinking I have more strength, willpower, and determination than I actually do, and so am also embarrassed I acted so weakly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For anyone who is familiar with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://naruto.fandom.com/wiki/Narutopedia&quot;&gt;Naruto&lt;/a&gt; series, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://naruto.fandom.com/wiki/Uchiha_Clan&quot;&gt;Uchiha Clan&lt;/a&gt; (which I once badly cosplayed) is a group of individuals who possess &lt;a href=&quot;https://naruto.fandom.com/wiki/Sharingan&quot;&gt;Sharingan&lt;/a&gt; eyes that grant them immense power.  These Sharingan eyes are awakened through experiencing intense feeling and emotion.  I am thoroughly convinced the ideal conditions for such an awakening are getting your heart shattered while sleep-deprived on a Tuesday night ..&lt;em&gt;cough cough&lt;/em&gt;..  But instead of gaining the ability to control &lt;a href=&quot;https://naruto.fandom.com/wiki/Kurama&quot;&gt;kyuubi&lt;/a&gt;, I just get self-loathing, intense stubbornness, and an oddly heightened athletic ability.  Indeed, I truly could have died from my own intense stubbornness if not saved by a close friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love causes one to live in denial, only to one day wake up and realize how much you compromised and degraded your own identity to conform to something you thought the other party wanted,  and then not even necessarily what they actually did.  I am ashamed and disappointed in myself but also know I’m naturally going to do the same thing again.  Perhaps just a quirk of my personality or thirst… (just kidding but maybe not actually just kidding).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yet again, I now have a bunch of bad soda that I have no idea what to do with.  Heaven forbid I become a sick fuck and actually decide to drink it.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lemon-la-croix/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lemon-la-croix/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dating</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Master of Romance</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After yet another long hiatus I am back again.  During my absence a lot has happened in the USA.  I often struggle to find suitable words to accurately express my inner thoughts, yet still feel compelled to convey something meaningful instead of regurgitating ideas others already fleshed out more eloquently.  The end result is a lack of blog posts and a very unpopular blog.  Furthermore, the truth is I am often just too unmotivated to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my time away from blogging I have tried several dating apps and feel like sharing my experiences.  The apps allow a glimpse into the parallel yet disparate realities inhabited by heterosexual men and women (as I lack the experience to write intelligently on LGBTQ+ dating), and has been very educational.  Below I will describe some general tips and guidelines and in my next post I will describe the apps I used and my experience in each one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Tips and Guidelines for Dating&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bad grammar is unpleasant and unattractive, be sure you are getting your verb tenses and punctuation down correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Having high standards can come off as bitchy (if you are a girl) or 
douche-ey (if you are a guy).  Do not let people shame you for having high 
standards.  From an evolutionary perspective being selective is vital 
to the survival of offspring…..  (^;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Avoid &quot;bad idea pictures&quot; because they are magnets for creepy comments: &quot;In a ball pit&quot;, &quot;Riding a horse&quot;, &quot;Mouth open with food inside&quot;, 
&quot;Swimming&quot;… The list expands with each passing day as creepy comments 
evolve to adapt - like an evolutionary game of cat-and-mouse.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Avoid creating a profile that is just a collection of cliches.  Examples 
include: &quot;new to the area&quot;, &quot;can make me laugh&quot;, &quot;foodie&quot;, or &quot;no hookups&quot;. Keep in mind that laughing gas makes people laugh too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Realize you will inevitably have to live with a guilty conscience for any 
deception used to obtain sexual intercourse.   This includes exaggerating 
to a partner more commitment than intended or optical illusion photography 
to disguise body weight.  Avoidance of this guilty conscience, assuming you have a conscience, incentivizes acting with honesty and integrity&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Realize you will eventually become too old and close to death to afford the 
time investment of dating.  With this understanding, avoid judgement based 
on superficial traits such as height, salary, or nose shape.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;While it is tempting to shrug off racial romantic preferences as natural or 
accidental, they are in fact guided by a larger racial hierarchy and are 
political in nature.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a final disclaimer, it is your dating life and not that of anyone else.  Greatness is not from blind obedience (much less blind obedience to some random dude's blog post), but from copying only that which is good.  I hope to see you all in the next blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side Note:  I am sorry for the harm caused by my previous posts.  I 
feel I should leave the posts untouched because editing them would be 
enacting revisionist history.  Through self-examination I hope to learn 
from my mistakes and in doing so strive to become a more knowledgeable and 
compassionate individual.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dating-advice/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/dating-advice/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dating</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 WEIRD Tricks to Change Your Life</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I was browsing the Internet and came across a &quot;Life Hack&quot; about how I could &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simplyrecipes.com/recipes/the_finger_test_to_check_the_doneness_of_meat/&quot;&gt;poke my hand&lt;/a&gt; to determine how raw or cooked a piece of meat was. I tried it out but it was not very effective as my hand is overly-rough and all of it feels like calloused skin D^'’: . Additionally the only way I cook meat is medium-rare so it wouldn’t have mattered anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was so disappointed with how LAME this &quot;Life Hack&quot; was that I was inspired to create a personal list of GENUINE Life Hacks. I believe these Life Hacks will legitimately improve someones quality of life, and I hope reading them brings you all enjoyment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you like drinking of Gatorade to replenish electrolytes but are too stingy to buy it? Try mixing apple cider vinegar, salt, honey, and water to create Bootleg Gatorade. It tastes absolutely &lt;strong&gt;VILE&lt;/strong&gt; but at least you are saving some money. Money which you can waste on being materialistic somewhere else. Bonus points for using organic honey and organic apple cider vinegar. Super-Bonus Points for using artisinal organic cider vinegar, raw-unfiltered wild honey, Hawaiian sea salt, and Fiji water, to create something that is both extremely vile and more expensive than just buying Gatorade in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you like eating ground beef but are too stingy to buy large amounts of it? Simply mix lentils and bread crumbs into your ground beef so that when you cook it, it appears as if you have created more meat than you actually purchased. To further decieve your taste buds, make the resulting mixture extra spicy so your mouth becomes too numb to tell the difference anyway. The same trick can also be applied to cake mix, by adding all-purpose flour to it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you like low sodium soy sauce but dislike that it costs the same price as regular sodium soy sauce? Simply buy regular sodium soy sauce and dilute it with water until the desired lower sodium concentration is reached. This also works for converting dark roast coffee into light roast coffee, albeit with a slight loss in quality.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you want to be rich but lack both the drive and ambition needed for accumulating wealth? Simply change your name to &quot;Rich&quot; so regardless of what your financial circumstances are you are &quot;rich&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you want to write a blog posts, but lack both sufficient talent and motivation? Lower your standards and &lt;a href=&quot;/settlements/&quot;&gt;SETTLE&lt;/a&gt; by making a list of unrelated items. Give this post a click-bait title so people are tricked into reading it. Gain delight from the fact that you have decieved people into reading your blog post (^:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/listicle/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/listicle/</guid>
        
        
        <category>lifehax</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love, Bitterness, and RAGE</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Perhaps one of the greatest advantages of being constantly in a state of bitterness and &lt;strong&gt;RAGE&lt;/strong&gt; is that I am able to redirect it towards self-improvement, where otherwise I would just be a very lazy person. I do this so often that I wonder if my internal rage and bitterness is now part of who I am as a person, such that giving it up would be losing a large part of my identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say this because the most common target for all this &lt;strong&gt;RAGE&lt;/strong&gt; is frequent exercise and trying to stay healthy. Even though at first it was probably entertainment, at this point exercise is now just a coping mechanism, as the pain and unpleasantness from lifting heavy objects is able to temporarily mask the pain and unpleasantness of my daily life. Additionally, I am never quite sure if soreness I have is actually legitimate muscular soreness, or if it is just the pain I feel from physically existing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I feel like setting a personal record, or even just lifting more than I usually do, I follow tips #2 and #3 stated in my earlier &lt;a href=&quot;/fitn-ness/&quot;&gt;fitness post&lt;/a&gt;. This consolidation of pure love for the &lt;a href=&quot;/vocaloid/&quot;&gt;waifu&lt;/a&gt;, general bitterness towards life, and &lt;strong&gt;RAGE&lt;/strong&gt; from past mistreatments is enough to help me power through super heavy sets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I have started and am still continuing on with a diet to lose a bit of weight and make myself super-fit. For this, I took a picture of myself every weekend to record my progress…. only to realize that all I actually accomplished was just &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/starving_everyday.png&quot;&gt;tooly pictures&lt;/a&gt; of myself every week for currently 4 weeks. Similar to before, they are mirror-selfies because I have no friends to take pics of me, and asking strangers for this is weird….. Just looking at them burns my soul, and it makes me feel like I belong at &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Home_Depot&quot;&gt;The Home Depot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My original goal was to post this completed collection to facebook, with the intent of getting at least 10 facebook likes, but I have gained enough foresight to know that I will certainly get extremely-cyber-bullied for doing this. Accordingly, I am limiting these ‘pics’ to solely my personal blog, as I am for sure not popular or well-known enough for anyone to come to my blog just to cyber-bully me. Also, my face is censored for identity theft reasons, but feel free to reach out if you want &lt;em&gt;uncensored&lt;/em&gt; ‘pics’ (^^^:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, after yet another long hiatus, I have returned to writing blog posts. Thanks to all who earnestly follow my blog, your support warms my heart and is sincerely appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/rage-drive/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/rage-drive/</guid>
        
        
        <category>fitness</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Special Blog Post (Fitness Edition)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Though I am not in any way trying to say I am more fitter than anyone else, I have done enough exercise to have learned a unique and helpful set of tips and tricks. For credibility, &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/fitness_pic.jpg&quot;&gt;here (NSFW)&lt;/a&gt; is a picture of me wearing my Black Rock Shooter hat and carrying some distilled water. I am really shy and self-conscious so please do not bully me. Also, I am taking a mirror-selfie because I have no friends to take pics of me, and it is awkward to ask this sort of thing to strangers. Without further word fluff, here are my four tips for successful fitness endeavors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Have your only source of potable water be the water fountain at the gym. When you run out of water and are &lt;strong&gt;THIRSTY&lt;/strong&gt; you have no choice but to go to the gym. This incentivizes you to work out so that your fellow gym-goers think you are one of them … and not just some dude who keeps stealing the water.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Imagine your &lt;a href=&quot;/vocaloid/&quot;&gt;beloved waifu&lt;/a&gt; is cheering you on so you have no choice but to do your very best to impress her. This technique is particularly effective if your waifu is a pure 2D maiden, who loves and appreciates all your hard work and dedication, rather than some disgusting 3DPD.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Channel the accumulated rage and hatred that you carry around and refuse to let go of. Imagine that you are violently and savagely murdering all your haters, despite their pleas for mercy (^:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Accept the fact that you are already dead inside, so even if the weight kills you not much is lost was lost as you were already dead to begin with. Realize that going to the gym is the only thing that gives you a temporary, albeit transient, feeling of being alive.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/fitn-ness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/fitn-ness/</guid>
        
        
        <category>fitness</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Old and Bitter</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday was my 24th birthday so I actively and wishfully checked my Facebook to see how many people would say Happy Birthday to me. This year around 5.8% of my friends in some way wished me Happy Birthday, which is nice, but I was greedily hoping for at least 10%. As a result, I will be bitter for the next couple of days, but will eventually let it go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have already compiled the names of those who wished me Happy Birthday into a “treat these people extremely kindly” list, and placed everyone else in a “did not wish me Happy Birthday in 2018” list. When society collapses I will reference these two lists to determine who to save during the subsequent Purge. These hypothetical conversations will begin with something along the lines of: “Remember that time you didn’t wish me Happy Birthday to me in 2018?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems every year the amount of people in the “treat kindly” list decreases, probably because I am a naturally reclusive individual, or because I am unpopular and unpleasant. I predict 2019 will be a lower percentage turnout, but I hope I am pleasantly (rather than unpleasantly) surprised.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/birthday2018/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/birthday2018/</guid>
        
        
        <category>birthday</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Blood is Salt</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As the new year approaches I feel like it is as good a time as any to reflect on and post about what has occurred this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year’s experiences have caused me to dislike most common social behaviors and strongly wish that those responsible for them would just go away. In other words my sodium levels have increased to the point that my blood is pretty much just highly corrosive seawater, and is getting continuously saltier every day. Among the most sodium inducing events in my life are things such as viewing social media, seeing people not re-rack their weights at the gym, and the annoying fashion sense of the bourgeoisie all around me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, I was always trying to think of ways I could change the behavior of others but lately I have mellowed out and &lt;a href=&quot;http://seanwang.org/settlements/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SETTLED&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on the fact that it is much better to simply mind my own business. Excess sodium consumption is avoided by focusing on my own personal happiness and letting others do so as well. Moreover, if their behavior is degenerate and causes self-inflicted misfortune, I can use schadenfreude to convert that misfortune into personal happiness. The process is similar to how plants use photosynthesis to convert carbon dioxide into glucose and oxygen, except carbon dioxide is the misfortune of others and glucose+oxygen is personal happiness. This also reminds me of the quote by Gandhi about being the change you want to see in the world, rather than trying to force that change onto others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if enough edginess has not already been infused into this post, I am also getting to that age where I sometimes use the Internet to search up people that have mistreated me in the past. Upon doing so, it is delightful to see that most of them have not ended up well. As mentioned already in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://seanwang.org/schadenfreudic/&quot;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;, bad things happening to bad people is not really “misfortune”, but is more appropriately called “justice.” Almost as if I were watching the movie &lt;em&gt;Titanic&lt;/em&gt;, it warms my heart and brings a tear to my eye to see that there is lots of “justice” occurring in the world. In fact, just today I randomly thought about someone who was unpleasant to me when I was younger, looked them up, and discovered that life has not treated them well. The increase in my happiness felt like believing once again that Santa exists and has left many presents for me underneath a Christmas tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, unrelated to everything above, I have recently a minor pay increase at my job. It is nothing significant to write home about, but nevertheless contributes to increasing my overall happiness. So far I have spent  ALLLL of it on financing my various frivolous pursuits… like organic food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special shoutouts to a special individual who made very stylish piece of clothing for me. 10/10 would recommend. Would spare from the Purge if society collapses (^: .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;❄❄Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays❄❄&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/saltiness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/saltiness/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on Productivity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, when I was in high school, I had a history teacher who attempted to teach me about the various kinds of economic and political systems. She did this by polling high school students on how we wanted our course grades to be decided, with each grading system analogous to a different social system:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capitalism:&lt;/strong&gt; Each student recieves a grade based on their individual performance throughout the various homeworks and tests.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socialism:&lt;/strong&gt; Each student recieves a grade based on the combination and average of all test and homework scores.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communism:&lt;/strong&gt; Everyone recieves a C regardless of what the performance on all tests and homeworks is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of the students in the class wanted “Capitalism”, with a handful of people choosing “Socialism”, and me all by myself with “Communism”. Since this was before I took any courses in economics, 16 year old me thought everyone in the class was super-dumb, as “Communism” was the only guaranteed way to pass without doing any sort of work. Furthermore I was also a disdainful and edgy proletariat: I thought that a ‘C’ was passing, and it was the insatiable &lt;strong&gt;greed&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;selfishness&lt;/strong&gt; of my filthy bourgeosie classmates causing them to arrogantly demand something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast-forward to the present, where I now understand economics enough to know that Communism is actually &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; a good idea, if anything because there are people like 16 year old me standing by ready to ruin it. Moreoever, Socialism is not that much better, since functionally it just means everyone immediately fails, or the productive people are demotivated by everyone leeching off of them. Unfortunately, Capitalism is the only way society can last, since no other system is able to peaceably harvest the productivity out of “Sean-type” individuals: people who are possibly ‘encouraged’ into productivity, but in any other system would just meander around and parasitically drain resources (or just get killed off in a labor camp).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon reaching this conclusion I was sort of amused, since I realized pretty much everything productive I have done with my life so far has been extrinsically rather than intrisically motivated. In an ideal world, I intrinsically desire eating, staying indoors, playing video games, and idling, and wish for nothing more than to partake in these activities every day. A younger version of me would have also wanted to protect and provide for a life partner and offspring but life experiences have persuaded me otherwise. Every other activity which is not in the above list requires extrinsic motivation, which typically is through money or other resources. Accordingly, any action which does not provide me with a greater capability of indulging in my intrinsic desires simply never gets done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting with after high school: I only went to college because because I was a sheeple and just did what everyone else was doing. I only stayed in because I realized modern society values and compensates smart educated people (rather than dumb uneducated ones). I studied engineering instead of grapefruit peeling or pineapple cutting because engineering career prospects are better (and because I was already a insanely good pineapple cutter). After I graduated college, I got a job because I realized the welfare department would not be willing to keep me alive, and did not want to burden my parents with that task either. Additionally, my current employer financially supported my college education, so I am both morally and legally obligated to be a good employee for them. Currently, In addition to working my day job, I am also furthering my education on the off-chance that one day the skills I acquire will result in a greater earning potential… that and I have a particular compulsion towards collecting certificates (^: . The point is that relative success is possible even with a lack of intrinsic personal ambition, and that none of these things would have been done if I had the wealth to passionately vegetate instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems people who are intrinsically interested in generating value, and possess the skills and talents necessary to do so, are already doing so. Moreover, even people who are &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; intrinsically interested &lt;strong&gt;NOR&lt;/strong&gt; skiiled and talented (i.e. ME) are pushed by a capitalistic society toward this endeavor. More or less, the majority of the population &lt;a href=&quot;http://seanwang.org/settlements/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SETTLES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; where they can produce the most value, but not necessarily obtain the most happiness. If instead society was oriented to allow people to pursue their passions, people would be happier, but the cost is a loss in productivity that would mean almost certain societal collapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then again, perhaps this is just my narcissism and ego at work, and the actual productivity lost from fellow passionate vegetables choosing not to work is not that much. To end, these are just miscellaneous ponderings I have as I go though my daily life. It is not like anyone reads this blog or is deeply concerned with what I have to say anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/idling/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/idling/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
