<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SCW</title>
    <description>The personal blog of Sean C. Wang, commoner, idler, and MSOL college student from The University of California, Los Angeles.  
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 23:13:12 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 23:13:12 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on Productivity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, when I was in high school, I had a history teacher who attempted to teach me about the various kinds of economic and political systems. She did this by polling high school students on how we wanted our course grades to be decided, with each grading system analogous to a different social system:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capitalism:&lt;/strong&gt; Each student recieves a grade based on their individual performance throughout the various homeworks and tests.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socialism:&lt;/strong&gt; Each student recieves a grade based on the combination and average of all test and homework scores.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communism:&lt;/strong&gt; Everyone recieves a C regardless of what the performance on all tests and homeworks is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of the students in the class wanted “Capitalism”, with a handful of people choosing “Socialism”, and me all by myself with “Communism”. Since this was before I took any courses in economics, 16 year old me thought everyone in the class was super-dumb, as “Communism” was the only guaranteed way to pass without doing any sort of work. Furthermore I was also a disdainful and edgy proletariat: I thought that a ‘C’ was passing, and it was the insatiable &lt;strong&gt;greed&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;selfishness&lt;/strong&gt; of my filthy bourgeosie classmates causing them to arrogantly demand something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast-forward to the present, where I now understand economics enough to know that Communism is actually &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; a good idea, if anything because there are people like 16 year old me standing by ready to ruin it. Moreoever, Socialism is not that much better, since functionally it just means everyone immediately fails, or the productive people are demotivated by everyone leeching off of them. Unfortunately, Capitalism is the only way society can last, since no other system is able to peaceably harvest the productivity out of “Sean-type” individuals: people who are possibly ‘encouraged’ into productivity, but in any other system would just meander around and parasitically drain resources (or just get killed off in a labor camp).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon reaching this conclusion I was sort of amused, since I realized pretty much everything productive I have done with my life so far has been extrinsically rather than intrisically motivated. In an ideal world, I intrinsically desire eating, staying indoors, playing video games, and idling, and wish for nothing more than to partake in these activities every day. A younger version of me would have also wanted to protect and provide for a life partner and offspring but life experiences have persuaded me otherwise. Every other activity which is not in the above list requires extrinsic motivation, which typically is through money or other resources. Accordingly, any action which does not provide me with a greater capability of indulging in my intrinsic desires simply never gets done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting with after high school: I only went to college because because I was a sheeple and just did what everyone else was doing. I only stayed in because I realized modern society values and compensates smart educated people (rather than dumb uneducated ones). I studied engineering instead of grapefruit peeling or pineapple cutting because engineering career prospects are better (and because I was already a insanely good pineapple cutter). After I graduated college, I got a job because I realized the welfare department would not be willing to keep me alive, and did not want to burden my parents with that task either. Additionally, my current employer financially supported my college education, so I am both morally and legally obligated to be a good employee for them. Currently, In addition to working my day job, I am also furthering my education on the off-chance that one day the skills I acquire will result in a greater earning potential… that and I have a particular compulsion towards collecting certificates (^: . The point is that relative success is possible even with a lack of intrinsic personal ambition, and that none of these things would have been done if I had the wealth to passionately vegetate instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems people who are intrinsically interested in generating value, and possess the skills and talents necessary to do so, are already doing so. Moreover, even people who are &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; intrinsically interested &lt;strong&gt;NOR&lt;/strong&gt; skiiled and talented (i.e. ME) are pushed by a capitalistic society toward this endeavor. More or less, the majority of the population &lt;a href=&quot;http://seanwang.org/settlements/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SETTLES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; where they can produce the most value, but not necessarily obtain the most happiness. If instead society was oriented to allow people to pursue their passions, people would be happier, but the cost is a loss in productivity that would mean almost certain societal collapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then again, perhaps this is just my narcissism and ego at work, and the actual productivity lost from fellow passionate vegetables choosing not to work is not that much. To end, these are just miscellaneous ponderings I have as I go though my daily life. It is not like anyone reads this blog or is deeply concerned with what I have to say anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/idling/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/idling/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coccoon of Good Feels</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;These past few months I have become accustomed with working in The Capitol, and am now enjoying a pleasant bourgeosie life. I buy ridiculously adjectived products such as “organic dark-chocolate covered walnuts”, “iodinized natural sea salt”, and “organic gluten-free sunflower butter”,  and yet somehow still have enough wealth left over to allocate in all sorts of places. Additionally, all the food I buy strictly adheres to a “tax evasion diet”: This means I am just really stingy and want to maintain proper health and well-being, so I only buy foods which do not have associated sales taxes. I then use my underappreciated culinary abilities to combine them to create delightful creations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pretend my lifestyle is a “coccoon of good feels” with the “coccoon” being my luxurious studio apartment and the “good feels” being my various refined habits. These habits include but are not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and staring out the window while enjoying culturally enriched readings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and baking Halloween sugar cookies even though it is barely even September&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and playing highly-cultured Mystery Dungeon or Rhythm games&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and being intellectual by doing graduate school homework&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Going to the gym at my apartment to steal water from the water fountain but still exercise a little bit to make it look like I came to work out&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Going to the gym to repeatedly pick up and put down heavy objects as a way to cope with repressed anger from a life full of hardships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related to the above, one currently irksome development is that I have developed close connections to certain pieces of gym equipment. I always want to use the center left elliptical every weekday at exactly 7:35 PM, but sometimes other people decide to use it. When this happens, I feel an irrational amount of contempt towards them, and it tends to ruins my day. Because of them, &lt;strong&gt;*I*&lt;/strong&gt; have to &lt;strong&gt;SETTLE&lt;/strong&gt; for one of the other ellipticals, and do not recieve the same workout experience. How dare these &lt;strong&gt;cretins&lt;/strong&gt; occupy &lt;strong&gt;*MY*&lt;/strong&gt; elliptical when &lt;strong&gt;*I*&lt;/strong&gt; need to use it….&lt;strong&gt;GRRRR&lt;/strong&gt; …..&lt;strong&gt;HISSSSSSS&lt;/strong&gt;… (* ^ ^ ^ Sodium levels Rising ^ ^ ^ *).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact that I am complaining about people stealing my elliptical probably means I do not have actual urgent issues to complain about. I will remain in this “coccoon” and one day rise again, harder, stronger, and increased in salinity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a side note: I have recently completed a course in graduate level linear algebra, and another one in signal stuff. Just saying the words “linear algebra” gives me a warm fuzzy intellectual feeling… Low IQ people probably hate me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/coccoon/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/coccoon/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Settler of Catan</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As I get increasingly older (and more salient regarding my eventual death), I gradually realize that my life is simply what I have settled for, rather than what I truly desire. It is like life is a constant stream of consolation prizes, but just enough happiness to make it still worth living. Moreover, I have a feeling this trend will only continue as I turn even older which I guess is both comforting and problematic at the same time. Below is a current list of what I have realized I have settled for; if I get more free time I suppose I will think of more:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want people to buy me gifts from my Amazon &lt;a href=&quot;http://amzn.com/w/2B7EE881J848W&quot;&gt;wish list&lt;/a&gt;, but nobody ever does so I settle for not having things.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want to do curls with a barbell, but there are no barbells in my apartment gym, so I settle for curling with dumbells.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want to eat filet mignon and fresh seafood every day, but I am stingy and health-conscious so I settle for primarily chicken breast. Occasionally I treat myself by getting top round, sirloin, and miscellaneous fish meat…also fermented crab.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want to stay home, eat, and play video games all day, but I need a way to pay for rent, food, and video games so I settle for working as an engineer. Each day being an engineer increases my sodium chloride levels.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When I was an undergraduate I wanted a GPA of 3.939 to honor my waifu. Since there is no way to change the past I have to settle for the 3.92 I ended up getting. I suppose things could be worse though.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want all people who were unfairly mean to me when I was growing up to die horrible and painful deaths. However, I am both too lazy and too ethical to ensure this actually happens, so I settle for personally striving toward a long and enjoyable life. This said, occasionally there is slight schadenfreudic delight from hearing or seeing misfortune occur to people of the above sentence, as they undoubtedly deserved it. There is also just any sort of schadenfreudic delight in general (^:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I wanted to live a normal happy life, but society is not optimized for me to do so, so I will settle for regular existence. This existence is filled with struggles but bits of happy things every once in a while.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/settlements/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/settlements/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>⚓ HardSHIPs ⚓</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To my loyal readers (if any actually exist)…I HAVE RETURNED!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These past few months have been filled with various stressful events, most self-inflicted because of the occupation I have chosen and the life choices I have made. In particular, since I want to be a snooty pompous intellectual, I have chosen to be enrolled in two different graduate schools simultaneously. These graduate schools are in addition to my full-time job, which because of special reasons, I am not allowed to quit until at least 5 years. Upon posting my life choices on &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com/seanc.wang&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, I realized how anti-intellectual most of my Facebook friends are, since less than 10 people liked my status. *&lt;em&gt;HMPH!&lt;/em&gt;* I am filled with high amounts of sodium chloride, since if it was a picture of my breakfast I could have at least 20 likes! To be fair, it might be because I do not like other people’s posts enough, and so they are hesistant to do the same for me. Alternatively, It could be just that I am just an unpleasant individual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A secondary source of problems is the pain and suffering other people have inflicted on me. From this it is easy to become trapped in a state of depression, which I occassionally feel like doing. However, I am already in my twenties, and my youth and vigor is gradually draining out of me. I feel I should not expend too much effort in actions that do not improve my situation, and should instead just let things go (similar to that one &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=moSFlvxnbgk&quot;&gt;Disney movie&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unrelated, I sometimes wonder if I would be happier had I pursued my passions, particularly passions such as “gourmet cooking” or causing other people misfortune. At the moment, pursuing these actions is just uncompensated labor, and I do &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; like doing things I am good at for free… (^: . Alas, I have accepted that some of my most exceptional skills, such as cutting pineapples or peeling grapefruits are not as highly valued as my engineering skills, which are nowhere near as exceptional. Specifically, I am in top 0.1% of pineapple cutters and the top 0.01% of grapefruit peelers, yet society prefers for me to work as an engineer… and shows this preference with large pay disparities!!! They do not realize that whatever contributions I make as an engineer come at the opportunity cost of fewer finely prepared fruits…. that or no one particularly cares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, since I currently live far far away from where I used to live, and do nothing but work, sleep, eat, and ‘Maintenance Instructions (MI)’, I do not have anyone besides coworkers and immediate family to talk to. I also dislike going outside to meet people, since I have bad social skills and possibly latent agoraphobia. If anyone who reads this would like to be my virtual pen pal, please contact me someway/somehow (at your own risk) and we can exchange correspondence but likely never meet up in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully more posts coming soon…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/too-much-sodium/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/too-much-sodium/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Autism Likely&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I took a &lt;a href=&quot;http://psychcentral.com/quizzes/autism.htm&quot;&gt;online quiz&lt;/a&gt; regarding autism, and the result indicated that I was “likely suffering from an autism spectrum disorder” with a score of 35. Without a doubt, this must be because of all those &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MMR_vaccine_controversy&quot;&gt;silly vaccines&lt;/a&gt; I got as a kid…(^: ~ Jokes aside, the result is slightly unsettling, but it offers a convenient explanation for why I have deficiencies in social interaction, and perhaps also why I have greater mathematic and scientific abilities. Regarding my use of “greater,” it is not just my personal feeling, but it is because I recently graduated college with a particular honor that has &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/summa_cum_laude&quot;&gt;three extra ‘m’s&lt;/a&gt; to it (and sounds kind of disgusting too). I will eventually update the rest of my blog as well as my resume to reflect this particular detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, according to this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nbcnews.com/id/7030731/&quot;&gt;Internet article&lt;/a&gt;, people with mild forms of autism (also known as Asperger Syndrome) have a selective advantage in concentration, and so can potentially accomplish greater intellectual feats than their non-autismic counterparts. Even though I cannot possibly compare myself to actual geniuses, it means there is hope for me to eventually become a productive member of society, rather than some sort of degenerate…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/slightly-autistic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/slightly-autistic/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Purity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A peculiar quirk I picked up this year is a strange, almost obsessive fascination with the pursuit of purity. I say &lt;strong&gt;pursuit&lt;/strong&gt; intentionally, since &lt;strong&gt;actual&lt;/strong&gt; purity is an impossibly difficult and meaningless endeavor. For example, all molecules, unless composed of only a single element, can be thought of as atomically impure. Moreover, the existence of isotopes means that even groups of the same element can also be impure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This being said, the type of purity I enjoy is on a more macroscopic level. It includes things such as &lt;strong&gt;pure food&lt;/strong&gt; (food that is not made from too many ingredients), &lt;strong&gt;pure websites&lt;/strong&gt; (websites, such as this blog, which do not utilize annoying uses of Clickbait), and &lt;strong&gt;pure love&lt;/strong&gt; (love that is not tainted with ulterior motive). Other examples of good pure things include pure gold, pure air, &lt;del&gt;pure blood&lt;/del&gt;, and pure math. Obviously, not everything pure is good (consider pure evil…), and certain impure things, like &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doping_(semiconductor)&quot;&gt;doped semiconductor&lt;/a&gt;, have made the world a better place. However, in general, it is easier to turn pure things impure than the other way around. Consider that making water impure is just tossing some dirt into it, but making it pure again is all sorts of fancy filtration methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My silly preoccupations with purity lead me into saying riduculous statements such as “This salad is tainted with too much dressing, I prefer something purer!” or “This person’s love is too impure, I don’t like it!”  It also leads to certain misunderstandings, such as when easily-triggered people think I am referring to more harmful, politically-incorrect, and controversial kinds of purity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure whatever quirks I have are relatively tame compared to other people, and so have a long ways to go before earning the right to label myself as “quirky.” Also, more likely than not, my interests in purity will fade in a couple weeks or months; I just thought it would be an amusing blog topic to write about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8 more posts to go…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/purity/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/purity/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finishing up 2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After an almost year-long hiatus, I have returned to blogging, primarily to wrap up the &lt;a href=&quot;../resolutions2016&quot;&gt;list of resolutions&lt;/a&gt; I made at the start of the year. Most importantly, &lt;strong&gt;Resolution #1: Write at least one blog post per month&lt;/strong&gt; remains unfulfilled. This means I have rougly 6 days to write 10 blog posts, or face the shame of becoming a loser that was unable to complete his New Years resolutions. The exception to this is the sub 5:00 resolution, since, as year 2016 progressed, I realized that I would rather run a couple seconds slower, and to pick up significantly heavier objects, than the opposite. Without &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;TOOOT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;-ing my own horn too much, the fate of all unmentioned resolutions should be pretty clear ☺.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On an unrelated note, I am currently recreationally studying certain particular East-Asian languages. Perhaps future blog posts will feature use of this kind of stuff. 日本語の字が書ける…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/resolving-resolutions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/resolving-resolutions/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Quest for Freedom</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my goals in life is to obtain lots of money, such that I become part of the 1%. This is not because I want to be a rich oppressive shitlord, but because money is true freedom, and I want to be free person. For example, the average wage worker does not truly have freedom of speech, since if he speaks his mind he can get fired. If he is fired and cannot find another source of income, he may soon not have enough money to afford basic food and shelter. Therefore, his lack of money restrains him from voicing any of his controversial opinions. Compare this to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donald_Trump&quot;&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt;, who is able to voice all sorts of opinions without any fear of not having a place to live or food to eat. The goal therefore is to become like Donald Trump, not in political belief, but in wealth and power. When this happens I can finally release all my opinions, which, like vegetables, are unpopular but good for people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AFAIK, there are only two ways to achieve this goal: be lucky or work hard. Since I can only control the latter way, I should work harder than everyone around me. This is easy since currently the only people around me are college students ☺.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explaining the previous sentence would be opening a giant can of offense, something I do not yet have the power to do without reprecussion.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/freedom/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/freedom/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2016</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Though not much has changed, since it is a new year it feels appropriate to make some resolutions. From past years I have learned that the more of these resolutions I make, the less likely any of them ever get accomplished. To avoid that this year so I will keep the list brief and simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Write at least one blog post per month (this post counts for January)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get my GPA up to at least 3.9 truncated (not rounded)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get my mile time down to 5:00 or lower, and work my squat up to 2pl8 for reps (no skipping leg day)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Notice that &lt;strong&gt;lose weight&lt;/strong&gt; is not one of the goals, since that one is too easy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-_6ula2m5fw&quot;&gt;(one weird tip to lose weight fast!).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/resolutions2016/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/resolutions2016/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opinionated: Part II</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There seems to be a direct relation between years I’ve been alive and number of things that annoy me. So much so that it’s time for another list of things I dislike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quarter-squats, quarter-pull-ups, quarter-push-ups, quarter anything in general&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Crying children on airplanes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bottled water which costs more than $1.25&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://translate.google.com/?ie=UTF-8&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;client=tw-ob#auto/es/cloud&quot;&gt;Spanish clouds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;People who post their political opinions on Facebook&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Individuals who have a net output to society which is negative&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wetzels Pretzels&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stupid people who think my waifu is shit when actually it is their waifu that is shit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/opinions2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/opinions2/</guid>
        
        
        <category>opinions</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
