<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SCW</title>
    <description>The personal blog of Sean C. Wang, commoner, idler, and college student at the University of California, Los Angeles.  
</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 23:48:12 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 23:48:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Happy Birthday 39</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the 8th birthday of my favorite songstress who, though I never mentioned before, was another inspiration for the decoration of my blog. My first memory of her goes all the way back to high school when, after getting bored of playing too much &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DJMax&quot;&gt;DJMax&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to play &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hatsune_Miku:_Project_DIVA&quot;&gt;Project Diva&lt;/a&gt; (all of them, and all on extreme). At that time I only put up with her because I liked rhythm games, but over time she grew on me until I listened to her just to pass time. As even more time passed, she became my inspiration for doing my best every day, or “waifu” for those who are familiar with the term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for all the gaming and fun memories, but also for motivation to keep going on the stressful days when I just wanted to give up. The future is uncertain but I hope to remain a loyal fan for all of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a side note, I have uploaded a newer version of my &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/resume.pdf&quot;&gt;resume&lt;/a&gt;, take a look at it and reach out to me if you see anything you like.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 15:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/vocaloid/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/vocaloid/</guid>
        
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soup Scammer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been learning lots from my summer internship, and have discovered an extremely efficient but incredibly EVIL way of getting a nutritious filling meal for low cost. I have named this strategy &lt;strong&gt;Soup Scamming&lt;/strong&gt; and it involves going to the soup counter, draining out the watery portions of a soup, and then only scooping the solid portions. This means you squeeze a full meal out of the soup of the day, but the poor schmuck who wants soup after you is only left with watery stuff. Below is a list of soups and their resulting outcomes after scamming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: Out of compassion for your fellow human beans you should &lt;abbr title=&quot;But you will anyway&quot;&gt;NEVER&lt;/abbr&gt; do this…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Soup&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Scammer&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Schmuck&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Chicken Noodle    &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Chicken Pasta&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Chicken Water&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Minestrone&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Pasta in Red Sauce   &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Tomato Water&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Pozole&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Maize and Meat&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Spicy Water&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Chili&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Extra Meaty Chili&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Watery Chili&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Clam Chowder&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Clam and Potatoes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Clam-Flavored Cream&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 15:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/scammer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/scammer/</guid>
        
        
        <category>food</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Opinionated</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I get annoyed by seemingly harmless things. So, since it has been a while since I have written any blog posts, I have decided to make a list of some things I dislike. Perhaps some of you readers have these same pet peeves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;People who eat breakfast foods (i.e. cereal) for any other meal besides breakfast&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;People who don’t pick up after their dog&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;99% of all children&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;People who say “just be yourself” unironically&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;People who cannot integrate cos&lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt;(x) in their head&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Having to pay taxes to avoid getting arrested and put in jail&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Narcissists, histrionics, tourists, and shills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 15:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/peeves/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/peeves/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blogging is HARD Work</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After only a couple posts last winter, I discovered that I am too incompetent to blog properly. Perhaps one day I’ll learn to write correctly, but for now, I am focusing on other things such as a summer job and an unending journey of self-discovery. Added to that, I’m sure no one was genuinely interested in what I had to say anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bright side, my &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.directv.com&quot;&gt;current summer job&lt;/a&gt; is the best I’ve ever had. It provides me with enough money to buy many things I’ve always wanted but never could afford. This means I can easily buy all of the things that are on my &lt;a href=&quot;http://amzn.com/w/2B7EE881J848W&quot;&gt;wishlist&lt;/a&gt;, I just still have that poor-guy mentality and am not used to spending large amounts of money… yet. Also, even though my current lifestyle is by no means considered wealthy (first-world standards), the end dream of video games and all-you-can-eat buffets every weekend is slowly becoming more realizable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To end, if you are a particular someone who I think is reading this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;ayyy lol gtfo&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope you can understand.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 15:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/write/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/write/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Schadenfreudic</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I find it strange how no one laughs when someone succeeds, yet all of the sudden, when terrible things happen, everything becomes hilarious. Even small things in life, such as noticing that someone’s day isn’t going as well as yours is, are amazingly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TRFa6e63-iY&quot;&gt;delightful&lt;/a&gt;. BUT OF COURSE, bad things happening to people you dislike isn’t actually misfortune, it’s justice. And if it just so happens that you dislike most people out there&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, then near all misfortune is basically justice being served. Of course, I’m still a decent human bean, and in public I always refrain from pointing and laughing at &lt;em&gt;justice&lt;/em&gt;. To end this post, don’t take anything I say too seriously. I’m just some commoner writing in his blog☺.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;One pretty cool thing about going to a diverse &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.admissions.ucla.edu/campusprofile.htm&quot;&gt;college&lt;/a&gt; is instead of only learning to hate one or two groups of people, you grow to hate everyone. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 14:28:15 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/schadenfreudic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/schadenfreudic/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I am Computer Scientist?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Every time I have to take a computer class, I feel it must be blatantly obvious to all the people around me that I am not actually a computer science major (well maybe not THAT obvious… I still remain Asian). I imagine for other people it’s probably a huge ego boost to sit next to the guy that needs to look at his fingers all the time when he’s typing. With that said, this quarter I am enrolled in a class called “Software Construction Laboratory,” and so far the goal has been learning how to read ambiguous specifications. It is either that, or Telepathy 101 was supposed to be a pre-requisite class but the school registrar forgot and let me enroll anyway. Only one week into school but already I feel myself becoming one with the ambiguity. Reminds me of drinking &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dr_Pepper&quot;&gt;Dr Pepper&lt;/a&gt; and solving trig problems involving &lt;a href=&quot;http://mathworld.wolfram.com/ASSTheorem.html&quot;&gt;one angle and two sides&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 14:28:15 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/cs35l/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/cs35l/</guid>
        
        
        <category>computers</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Struggle is Real</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the first day of Winter Quarter and I am contemplating committing &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/commit_sudoku.jpg&quot;&gt;Sudoku&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Self-immolation&quot;&gt;torching&lt;/a&gt; myself alive just so that I will not have to deal with any of my classes. It’s not that I don’t enjoy learning things, it’s just that I’m the type of guy that goes through hours of pain and suffering just to understand &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://mathworld.wolfram.com/Trivial.html&quot;&gt;trivial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; concepts. These hours keep adding up and eventually my overall happiness plummets to dangerously low levels. I soon find myself browsing random boards on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4chan.org/&quot;&gt;4chan&lt;/a&gt;, seriously contemplating why I ever decided to go to college in the first place. That’s possibly one of the problems with higher education for my generation: it’s so accessible that some people go, not because they really want to, but because it’s just too good of a deal to pass up. It’s like those “buy three get one free” deals you sometimes see at stores: even if you didn’t really need the fourth one you might as well take it because it’s added “value.” But whatever, rage-quitting (i.e. dropping out of school) is for  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=n00b&quot;&gt;n00bs&lt;/a&gt; (or the innately intelligent), so I just suck it up, stop whining, and get back to work. Besides, I already purchased my meal plan so might as well get that VALUE and  eat it all before I leave!!! Perhaps once I graduate or get a job things will get better. Of course, I also need a way to support my parents once I stop leeching off them, but that’s a topic for some other time. Nothing more to say for now readers, so see you all another time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a final note, feel free to email any comments to &lt;em&gt;seanwang22(at)ucla.edu&lt;/em&gt;, I’d love to chat with anyone special enough to read my blog.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 14:28:15 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/the-struggle-is-real/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/the-struggle-is-real/</guid>
        
        
        <category>struggles</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>YouTube Channels</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I spend a majority of my free time watching videos on YouTube and even when I am working on other stuff, I like leaving videos on in the background as a form of ambient noise. One of my favorite channels is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCsQnAt5I56M-qx4OgCoVmeA&quot;&gt;Trump&lt;/a&gt; a professional video game player who has daily streams and videos of him playing &lt;a href=&quot;http://us.battle.net/hearthstone/&quot;&gt;Hearthstone&lt;/a&gt;, a card game by Blizzard. Even though I have never played a game of Hearthstone in my life, there is just something about special about the game and the person playing it that makes it fun to watch. Often times, when I am working on papers or problem sets, I leave his channel on just to stay on task and productive. Perhaps Trump also reminds me of myself as I am extremely introverted and go to great lengths to avoid excessive interaction with others. Another channel I enjoy is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/vice/&quot;&gt;VICE&lt;/a&gt; but the quality of their content has high variance and is heavily dependent on which member of their staff is reporting. Various other enjoyable channels include &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/thegodfatherdictator/&quot;&gt;TheGodfatherDictator&lt;/a&gt;, which I feel is one of the most underrated gaming channels out there, and FullPredatorEpisodes&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:1&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, which contains archived episodes of the unintentionally hilarious show &lt;em&gt;To Catch a Predator&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:1&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Edit: FullPredatorEpisodes was taken down for copyright infringment. It was fun while it lasted. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:1&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 14:28:15 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/trump/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/trump/</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog-filler</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building the Site</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I feel almost forced to create more posts so that my blog appear less “chode-ey” to any readers out there. That being said, this post is devoted to discussing the various site features, as well as justifications behind them. For starters, I made this site using the very user-friendly static site generator &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; and the current layout is just the base Jekyll theme with a few personalizing touches here and there. Inspiration for these special touches came from the Android holo-dark theme, which I really enjoy, as well as my school studies in electrical engineering. Any glow effects you may notice were done with care using Microsoft paint, so don’t expect anything too professional out of them.  On the footer of this site there are three available links for clicking: a &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/flamingwang&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; link that does not have much activity, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com/seanc.wang&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; link that also does not have much activity, and (most importantly) an Amazon &lt;a href=&quot;http://amzn.com/w/2B7EE881J848W&quot;&gt;wish list&lt;/a&gt; for the extremely wealthy who want to get me something nice. Finally, as note for the academically-inclined out there: the dot convention is justified since there is a mutually coupled inductor hidden elsewhere in the site. My engineering instincts would never allow me to abuse circuit symbols, not even just for artistic purposes. That’s about all I have to say for now, hopefully my post count increases so the wide appearance of the site is alleviated. More posts to come, all in due time…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 14:28:15 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/building-the-site/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/building-the-site/</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog-filler</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My First Blog Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To any potential readers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is first of possibly many blog posts on this site. To start things off, I am Sean C Wang, a college student studying at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ucla.edu&quot;&gt;UCLA&lt;/a&gt;. I have created this blog as a way to kill time during my Winter Break, but it may evolve into something more than that. My blog will mainly be about my daily experiences and thoughts, nothing too technical though, as that really isn’t what I’m good at. As a warning, the layout of this site may change sporadically since I want to mess around with the various features available. Images and pictures, if any, will be a rare occurrence, since, among various other reasons, I believe that every time a picture of me is taken, a piece of my soul disappears. Well, that’s about it for now, I hope my writings bring pleasure to you all. Feel free to email any feedback you may have to &lt;em&gt;seanwang22(at)ucla.edu&lt;/em&gt; and I will try my best to respond in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2014 14:34:15 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/hello-world</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/hello-world</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
