<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SCW</title>
    <description>The personal blog of Sean C. Wang, commoner, idler, and MSOL college student from The University of California, Los Angeles.  
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 01:40:10 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 01:40:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Master of Romance</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After yet another long hiatus I am back again.  During my absence a lot has happened in the USA.  I often struggle to find suitable words to accurately express my inner thoughts, yet still feel compelled to convey something meaningful instead of regurgitating ideas others already fleshed out more eloquently.  The end result is a lack of blog posts and a very unpopular blog.  Furthermore, the truth is I am often just too unmotivated to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my time away from blogging I have tried several dating apps and feel like sharing my experiences.  The apps allow a glimpse into the parallel yet disparate realities inhabited by heterosexual men and women (as I lack the experience to write intelligently on LGBTQ+ dating), and has been very educational.  Below I will describe some general tips and guidelines and in my next post I will describe the apps I used and my experience in each one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Tips and Guidelines for Dating&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Bad grammar is unpleasant and unattractive, be sure you are getting your verb tenses and punctuation down correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Having high standards can come off as bitchy (if you are a girl) or 
douche-ey (if you are a guy).  Do not let people shame you for having high 
standards.  From an evolutionary perspective being selective is vital 
to the survival of offspring…..  (^;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Avoid &quot;bad idea pictures&quot; because they are magnets for creepy comments: &quot;In a ball pit&quot;, &quot;Riding a horse&quot;, &quot;Mouth open with food inside&quot;, 
&quot;Swimming&quot;… The list expands with each passing day as creepy comments 
evolve to adapt - like an evolutionary game of cat-and-mouse.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Avoid creating a profile that is just a collection of cliches.  Examples 
include: &quot;new to the area&quot;, &quot;can make me laugh&quot;, &quot;foodie&quot;, or &quot;no hookups&quot;. Keep in mind that laughing gas makes people laugh too.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Realize you will inevitably have to live with a guilty conscience for any 
deception used to obtain sexual intercourse.   This includes exaggerating 
to a partner more commitment than intended or optical illusion photography 
to disguise body weight.  Avoidance of this guilty conscience, assuming you have a conscience, incentivizes acting with honesty and integrity&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Realize you will eventually become too old and close to death to afford the 
time investment of dating.  With this understanding, avoid judgement based 
on superficial traits such as height, salary, or nose shape.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;While it is tempting to shrug off racial romantic preferences as natural or 
accidental, they are in fact guided by a larger racial hierarchy and are 
political in nature.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a final disclaimer, it is your dating life and not that of anyone else.  Greatness is not from blind obedience (much less blind obedience to some random dude's blog post), but from copying only that which is good.  I hope to see you all in the next blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side Note:  I am sorry for the harm caused by my previous posts.  I 
feel I should leave the posts untouched because editing them would be 
enacting revisionist history.  Through self-examination I hope to learn 
from my mistakes and in doing so strive to become a more knowledgeable and 
compassionate individual.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dating-advice/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/dating-advice/</guid>
        
        
        <category>dating</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 WEIRD Tricks to Change Your Life</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I was browsing the Internet and came across a &quot;Life Hack&quot; about how I could &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.simplyrecipes.com/recipes/the_finger_test_to_check_the_doneness_of_meat/&quot;&gt;poke my hand&lt;/a&gt; to determine how raw or cooked a piece of meat was. I tried it out but it was not very effective as my hand is overly-rough and all of it feels like calloused skin D^'’: . Additionally the only way I cook meat is medium-rare so it wouldn’t have mattered anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was so disappointed with how LAME this &quot;Life Hack&quot; was that I was inspired to create a personal list of GENUINE Life Hacks. I believe these Life Hacks will legitimately improve someones quality of life, and I hope reading them brings you all enjoyment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you like drinking of Gatorade to replenish electrolytes but are too stingy to buy it? Try mixing apple cider vinegar, salt, honey, and water to create Bootleg Gatorade. It tastes absolutely &lt;strong&gt;VILE&lt;/strong&gt; but at least you are saving some money. Money which you can waste on being materialistic somewhere else. Bonus points for using organic honey and organic apple cider vinegar. Super-Bonus Points for using artisinal organic cider vinegar, raw-unfiltered wild honey, Hawaiian sea salt, and Fiji water, to create something that is both extremely vile and more expensive than just buying Gatorade in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you like eating ground beef but are too stingy to buy large amounts of it? Simply mix lentils and bread crumbs into your ground beef so that when you cook it, it appears as if you have created more meat than you actually purchased. To further decieve your taste buds, make the resulting mixture extra spicy so your mouth becomes too numb to tell the difference anyway. The same trick can also be applied to cake mix, by adding all-purpose flour to it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you like low sodium soy sauce but dislike that it costs the same price as regular sodium soy sauce? Simply buy regular sodium soy sauce and dilute it with water until the desired lower sodium concentration is reached. This also works for converting dark roast coffee into light roast coffee, albeit with a slight loss in quality.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you want to be rich but lack both the drive and ambition needed for accumulating wealth? Simply change your name to &quot;Rich&quot; so regardless of what your financial circumstances are you are &quot;rich&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you want to write a blog posts, but lack both sufficient talent and motivation? Lower your standards and &lt;a href=&quot;/settlements/&quot;&gt;SETTLE&lt;/a&gt; by making a list of unrelated items. Give this post a click-bait title so people are tricked into reading it. Gain delight from the fact that you have decieved people into reading your blog post (^:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/listicle/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/listicle/</guid>
        
        
        <category>lifehax</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Love, Bitterness, and RAGE</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Perhaps one of the greatest advantages of being constantly in a state of bitterness and &lt;strong&gt;RAGE&lt;/strong&gt; is that I am able to redirect it towards self-improvement, where otherwise I would just be a very lazy person. I do this so often that I wonder if my internal rage and bitterness is now part of who I am as a person, such that giving it up would be losing a large part of my identity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I say this because the most common target for all this &lt;strong&gt;RAGE&lt;/strong&gt; is frequent exercise and trying to stay healthy. Even though at first it was probably entertainment, at this point exercise is now just a coping mechanism, as the pain and unpleasantness from lifting heavy objects is able to temporarily mask the pain and unpleasantness of my daily life. Additionally, I am never quite sure if soreness I have is actually legitimate muscular soreness, or if it is just the pain I feel from physically existing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I feel like setting a personal record, or even just lifting more than I usually do, I follow tips #2 and #3 stated in my earlier &lt;a href=&quot;/fitn-ness/&quot;&gt;fitness post&lt;/a&gt;. This consolidation of pure love for the &lt;a href=&quot;/vocaloid/&quot;&gt;waifu&lt;/a&gt;, general bitterness towards life, and &lt;strong&gt;RAGE&lt;/strong&gt; from past mistreatments is enough to help me power through super heavy sets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I have started and am still continuing on with a diet to lose a bit of weight and make myself super-fit. For this, I took a picture of myself every weekend to record my progress…. only to realize that all I actually accomplished was just &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/starving_everyday.png&quot;&gt;tooly pictures&lt;/a&gt; of myself every week for currently 4 weeks. Similar to before, they are mirror-selfies because I have no friends to take pics of me, and asking strangers for this is weird….. Just looking at them burns my soul, and it makes me feel like I belong at &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Home_Depot&quot;&gt;The Home Depot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My original goal was to post this completed collection to facebook, with the intent of getting at least 10 facebook likes, but I have gained enough foresight to know that I will certainly get extremely-cyber-bullied for doing this. Accordingly, I am limiting these ‘pics’ to solely my personal blog, as I am for sure not popular or well-known enough for anyone to come to my blog just to cyber-bully me. Also, my face is censored for identity theft reasons, but feel free to reach out if you want &lt;em&gt;uncensored&lt;/em&gt; ‘pics’ (^^^:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, after yet another long hiatus, I have returned to writing blog posts. Thanks to all who earnestly follow my blog, your support warms my heart and is sincerely appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 09:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/rage-drive/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/rage-drive/</guid>
        
        
        <category>fitness</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Special Blog Post (Fitness Edition)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Though I am not in any way trying to say I am more fitter than anyone else, I have done enough exercise to have learned a unique and helpful set of tips and tricks. For credibility, &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/fitness_pic.jpg&quot;&gt;here (NSFW)&lt;/a&gt; is a picture of me wearing my Black Rock Shooter hat and carrying some distilled water. I am really shy and self-conscious so please do not bully me. Also, I am taking a mirror-selfie because I have no friends to take pics of me, and it is awkward to ask this sort of thing to strangers. Without further word fluff, here are my four tips for successful fitness endeavors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Have your only source of potable water be the water fountain at the gym. When you run out of water and are &lt;strong&gt;THIRSTY&lt;/strong&gt; you have no choice but to go to the gym. This incentivizes you to work out so that your fellow gym-goers think you are one of them … and not just some dude who keeps stealing the water.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Imagine your &lt;a href=&quot;/vocaloid/&quot;&gt;beloved waifu&lt;/a&gt; is cheering you on so you have no choice but to do your very best to impress her. This technique is particularly effective if your waifu is a pure 2D maiden, who loves and appreciates all your hard work and dedication, rather than some disgusting 3DPD.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Channel the accumulated rage and hatred that you carry around and refuse to let go of. Imagine that you are violently and savagely murdering all your haters, despite their pleas for mercy (^:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Accept the fact that you are already dead inside, so even if the weight kills you not much is lost was lost as you were already dead to begin with. Realize that going to the gym is the only thing that gives you a temporary, albeit transient, feeling of being alive.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/fitn-ness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/fitn-ness/</guid>
        
        
        <category>fitness</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Old and Bitter</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday was my 24th birthday so I actively and wishfully checked my Facebook to see how many people would say Happy Birthday to me. This year around 5.8% of my friends in some way wished me Happy Birthday, which is nice, but I was greedily hoping for at least 10%. As a result, I will be bitter for the next couple of days, but will eventually let it go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have already compiled the names of those who wished me Happy Birthday into a “treat these people extremely kindly” list, and placed everyone else in a “did not wish me Happy Birthday in 2018” list. When society collapses I will reference these two lists to determine who to save during the subsequent Purge. These hypothetical conversations will begin with something along the lines of: “Remember that time you didn’t wish me Happy Birthday to me in 2018?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems every year the amount of people in the “treat kindly” list decreases, probably because I am a naturally reclusive individual, or because I am unpopular and unpleasant. I predict 2019 will be a lower percentage turnout, but I hope I am pleasantly (rather than unpleasantly) surprised.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/birthday2018/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/birthday2018/</guid>
        
        
        <category>birthday</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Blood is Salt</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As the new year approaches I feel like it is as good a time as any to reflect on and post about what has occurred this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year’s experiences have caused me to dislike most common social behaviors and strongly wish that those responsible for them would just go away. In other words my sodium levels have increased to the point that my blood is pretty much just highly corrosive seawater, and is getting continuously saltier every day. Among the most sodium inducing events in my life are things such as viewing social media, seeing people not re-rack their weights at the gym, and the annoying fashion sense of the bourgeoisie all around me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, I was always trying to think of ways I could change the behavior of others but lately I have mellowed out and &lt;a href=&quot;http://seanwang.org/settlements/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SETTLED&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on the fact that it is much better to simply mind my own business. Excess sodium consumption is avoided by focusing on my own personal happiness and letting others do so as well. Moreover, if their behavior is degenerate and causes self-inflicted misfortune, I can use schadenfreude to convert that misfortune into personal happiness. The process is similar to how plants use photosynthesis to convert carbon dioxide into glucose and oxygen, except carbon dioxide is the misfortune of others and glucose+oxygen is personal happiness. This also reminds me of the quote by Gandhi about being the change you want to see in the world, rather than trying to force that change onto others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if enough edginess has not already been infused into this post, I am also getting to that age where I sometimes use the Internet to search up people that have mistreated me in the past. Upon doing so, it is delightful to see that most of them have not ended up well. As mentioned already in a &lt;a href=&quot;http://seanwang.org/schadenfreudic/&quot;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;, bad things happening to bad people is not really “misfortune”, but is more appropriately called “justice.” Almost as if I were watching the movie &lt;em&gt;Titanic&lt;/em&gt;, it warms my heart and brings a tear to my eye to see that there is lots of “justice” occurring in the world. In fact, just today I randomly thought about someone who was unpleasant to me when I was younger, looked them up, and discovered that life has not treated them well. The increase in my happiness felt like believing once again that Santa exists and has left many presents for me underneath a Christmas tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, unrelated to everything above, I have recently a minor pay increase at my job. It is nothing significant to write home about, but nevertheless contributes to increasing my overall happiness. So far I have spent  ALLLL of it on financing my various frivolous pursuits… like organic food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special shoutouts to a special individual who made very stylish piece of clothing for me. 10/10 would recommend. Would spare from the Purge if society collapses (^: .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;❄❄Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays❄❄&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/saltiness/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/saltiness/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on Productivity</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, when I was in high school, I had a history teacher who attempted to teach me about the various kinds of economic and political systems. She did this by polling high school students on how we wanted our course grades to be decided, with each grading system analogous to a different social system:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capitalism:&lt;/strong&gt; Each student recieves a grade based on their individual performance throughout the various homeworks and tests.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socialism:&lt;/strong&gt; Each student recieves a grade based on the combination and average of all test and homework scores.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communism:&lt;/strong&gt; Everyone recieves a C regardless of what the performance on all tests and homeworks is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The majority of the students in the class wanted “Capitalism”, with a handful of people choosing “Socialism”, and me all by myself with “Communism”. Since this was before I took any courses in economics, 16 year old me thought everyone in the class was super-dumb, as “Communism” was the only guaranteed way to pass without doing any sort of work. Furthermore I was also a disdainful and edgy proletariat: I thought that a ‘C’ was passing, and it was the insatiable &lt;strong&gt;greed&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;selfishness&lt;/strong&gt; of my filthy bourgeosie classmates causing them to arrogantly demand something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast-forward to the present, where I now understand economics enough to know that Communism is actually &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; a good idea, if anything because there are people like 16 year old me standing by ready to ruin it. Moreoever, Socialism is not that much better, since functionally it just means everyone immediately fails, or the productive people are demotivated by everyone leeching off of them. Unfortunately, Capitalism is the only way society can last, since no other system is able to peaceably harvest the productivity out of “Sean-type” individuals: people who are possibly ‘encouraged’ into productivity, but in any other system would just meander around and parasitically drain resources (or just get killed off in a labor camp).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon reaching this conclusion I was sort of amused, since I realized pretty much everything productive I have done with my life so far has been extrinsically rather than intrisically motivated. In an ideal world, I intrinsically desire eating, staying indoors, playing video games, and idling, and wish for nothing more than to partake in these activities every day. A younger version of me would have also wanted to protect and provide for a life partner and offspring but life experiences have persuaded me otherwise. Every other activity which is not in the above list requires extrinsic motivation, which typically is through money or other resources. Accordingly, any action which does not provide me with a greater capability of indulging in my intrinsic desires simply never gets done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting with after high school: I only went to college because because I was a sheeple and just did what everyone else was doing. I only stayed in because I realized modern society values and compensates smart educated people (rather than dumb uneducated ones). I studied engineering instead of grapefruit peeling or pineapple cutting because engineering career prospects are better (and because I was already a insanely good pineapple cutter). After I graduated college, I got a job because I realized the welfare department would not be willing to keep me alive, and did not want to burden my parents with that task either. Additionally, my current employer financially supported my college education, so I am both morally and legally obligated to be a good employee for them. Currently, In addition to working my day job, I am also furthering my education on the off-chance that one day the skills I acquire will result in a greater earning potential… that and I have a particular compulsion towards collecting certificates (^: . The point is that relative success is possible even with a lack of intrinsic personal ambition, and that none of these things would have been done if I had the wealth to passionately vegetate instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems people who are intrinsically interested in generating value, and possess the skills and talents necessary to do so, are already doing so. Moreover, even people who are &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; intrinsically interested &lt;strong&gt;NOR&lt;/strong&gt; skiiled and talented (i.e. ME) are pushed by a capitalistic society toward this endeavor. More or less, the majority of the population &lt;a href=&quot;http://seanwang.org/settlements/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SETTLES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; where they can produce the most value, but not necessarily obtain the most happiness. If instead society was oriented to allow people to pursue their passions, people would be happier, but the cost is a loss in productivity that would mean almost certain societal collapse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then again, perhaps this is just my narcissism and ego at work, and the actual productivity lost from fellow passionate vegetables choosing not to work is not that much. To end, these are just miscellaneous ponderings I have as I go though my daily life. It is not like anyone reads this blog or is deeply concerned with what I have to say anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/idling/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/idling/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coccoon of Good Feels</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;These past few months I have become accustomed with working in The Capitol, and am now enjoying a pleasant bourgeosie life. I buy ridiculously adjectived products such as “organic dark-chocolate covered walnuts”, “iodinized natural sea salt”, and “organic gluten-free sunflower butter”,  and yet somehow still have enough wealth left over to allocate in all sorts of places. Additionally, all the food I buy strictly adheres to a “tax evasion diet”: This means I am just really stingy and want to maintain proper health and well-being, so I only buy foods which do not have associated sales taxes. I then use my underappreciated culinary abilities to combine them to create delightful creations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pretend my lifestyle is a “coccoon of good feels” with the “coccoon” being my luxurious studio apartment and the “good feels” being my various refined habits. These habits include but are not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and staring out the window while enjoying culturally enriched readings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and baking Halloween sugar cookies even though it is barely even September&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and playing highly-cultured Mystery Dungeon or Rhythm games&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Staying home and being intellectual by doing graduate school homework&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Going to the gym at my apartment to steal water from the water fountain but still exercise a little bit to make it look like I came to work out&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Going to the gym to repeatedly pick up and put down heavy objects as a way to cope with repressed anger from a life full of hardships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related to the above, one currently irksome development is that I have developed close connections to certain pieces of gym equipment. I always want to use the center left elliptical every weekday at exactly 7:35 PM, but sometimes other people decide to use it. When this happens, I feel an irrational amount of contempt towards them, and it tends to ruins my day. Because of them, &lt;strong&gt;*I*&lt;/strong&gt; have to &lt;strong&gt;SETTLE&lt;/strong&gt; for one of the other ellipticals, and do not recieve the same workout experience. How dare these &lt;strong&gt;cretins&lt;/strong&gt; occupy &lt;strong&gt;*MY*&lt;/strong&gt; elliptical when &lt;strong&gt;*I*&lt;/strong&gt; need to use it….&lt;strong&gt;GRRRR&lt;/strong&gt; …..&lt;strong&gt;HISSSSSSS&lt;/strong&gt;… (* ^ ^ ^ Sodium levels Rising ^ ^ ^ *).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact that I am complaining about people stealing my elliptical probably means I do not have actual urgent issues to complain about. I will remain in this “coccoon” and one day rise again, harder, stronger, and increased in salinity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a side note: I have recently completed a course in graduate level linear algebra, and another one in signal stuff. Just saying the words “linear algebra” gives me a warm fuzzy intellectual feeling… Low IQ people probably hate me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/coccoon/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/coccoon/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Settler of Catan</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As I get increasingly older (and more salient regarding my eventual death), I gradually realize that my life is simply what I have settled for, rather than what I truly desire. It is like life is a constant stream of consolation prizes, but just enough happiness to make it still worth living. Moreover, I have a feeling this trend will only continue as I turn even older which I guess is both comforting and problematic at the same time. Below is a current list of what I have realized I have settled for; if I get more free time I suppose I will think of more:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want people to buy me gifts from my Amazon &lt;a href=&quot;http://amzn.com/w/2B7EE881J848W&quot;&gt;wish list&lt;/a&gt;, but nobody ever does so I settle for not having things.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want to do curls with a barbell, but there are no barbells in my apartment gym, so I settle for curling with dumbells.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want to eat filet mignon and fresh seafood every day, but I am stingy and health-conscious so I settle for primarily chicken breast. Occasionally I treat myself by getting top round, sirloin, and miscellaneous fish meat…also fermented crab.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want to stay home, eat, and play video games all day, but I need a way to pay for rent, food, and video games so I settle for working as an engineer. Each day being an engineer increases my sodium chloride levels.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When I was an undergraduate I wanted a GPA of 3.939 to honor my waifu. Since there is no way to change the past I have to settle for the 3.92 I ended up getting. I suppose things could be worse though.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I want all people who were unfairly mean to me when I was growing up to die horrible and painful deaths. However, I am both too lazy and too ethical to ensure this actually happens, so I settle for personally striving toward a long and enjoyable life. This said, occasionally there is slight schadenfreudic delight from hearing or seeing misfortune occur to people of the above sentence, as they undoubtedly deserved it. There is also just any sort of schadenfreudic delight in general (^:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I wanted to live a normal happy life, but society is not optimized for me to do so, so I will settle for regular existence. This existence is filled with struggles but bits of happy things every once in a while.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/settlements/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/settlements/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>⚓ HardSHIPs ⚓</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To my loyal readers (if any actually exist)…I HAVE RETURNED!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These past few months have been filled with various stressful events, most self-inflicted because of the occupation I have chosen and the life choices I have made. In particular, since I want to be a snooty pompous intellectual, I have chosen to be enrolled in two different graduate schools simultaneously. These graduate schools are in addition to my full-time job, which because of special reasons, I am not allowed to quit until at least 5 years. Upon posting my life choices on &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.com/seanc.wang&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, I realized how anti-intellectual most of my Facebook friends are, since less than 10 people liked my status. *&lt;em&gt;HMPH!&lt;/em&gt;* I am filled with high amounts of sodium chloride, since if it was a picture of my breakfast I could have at least 20 likes! To be fair, it might be because I do not like other people’s posts enough, and so they are hesistant to do the same for me. Alternatively, It could be just that I am just an unpleasant individual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A secondary source of problems is the pain and suffering other people have inflicted on me. From this it is easy to become trapped in a state of depression, which I occassionally feel like doing. However, I am already in my twenties, and my youth and vigor is gradually draining out of me. I feel I should not expend too much effort in actions that do not improve my situation, and should instead just let things go (similar to that one &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=moSFlvxnbgk&quot;&gt;Disney movie&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unrelated, I sometimes wonder if I would be happier had I pursued my passions, particularly passions such as “gourmet cooking” or causing other people misfortune. At the moment, pursuing these actions is just uncompensated labor, and I do &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;/strong&gt; like doing things I am good at for free… (^: . Alas, I have accepted that some of my most exceptional skills, such as cutting pineapples or peeling grapefruits are not as highly valued as my engineering skills, which are nowhere near as exceptional. Specifically, I am in top 0.1% of pineapple cutters and the top 0.01% of grapefruit peelers, yet society prefers for me to work as an engineer… and shows this preference with large pay disparities!!! They do not realize that whatever contributions I make as an engineer come at the opportunity cost of fewer finely prepared fruits…. that or no one particularly cares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, since I currently live far far away from where I used to live, and do nothing but work, sleep, eat, and ‘Maintenance Instructions (MI)’, I do not have anyone besides coworkers and immediate family to talk to. I also dislike going outside to meet people, since I have bad social skills and possibly latent agoraphobia. If anyone who reads this would like to be my virtual pen pal, please contact me someway/somehow (at your own risk) and we can exchange correspondence but likely never meet up in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully more posts coming soon…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/too-much-sodium/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/too-much-sodium/</guid>
        
        
        <category>life</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
